谢谢  你嘴真甜
Thank you. Aren't you sweet.
我们去查查大学里
Let's go check to see if the university
还有没有氦气存货吧
has any helium in reserve.
你知道我今天差点就不穿这件衣服吗
Did you know that I almost didn't wear this shirt today?
巴里  我们碰到了麻烦
Hey, Barry, we're in trouble.
我们需要液氦
We need liquid helium--
系里有多余的可以让我们用吗
does the department have any we can use?
抱歉  这东西有些短缺
Sorry, there's a shortage.
而仅有的存货  我要拿来做量子激发研究
And what we do have I need for my quantum excitation study.
你那个实验不需要用多少啊
But you won't need much for that.
的确  但如果成功了
True, but if it's successful,
我开派对要拿来灌气球啊
I'm having a party with balloons.
别这样  巴里  有个瑞典团队
Come on, Barry, there's a Swedish team
想抢先进行我们的实验
trying to run our experiment before us.
你真不能匀一点给我们吗
Can't you spare any?
你们老实说  如果今天换我碰到这情况
Be honest-- if the shoe was on the other foot,